http://www.chamberlin.co.uk/site-essentials/privacy-notice

HomeAbout ChamberlinOur StrategyMarket FactorsOur HistoryThe BoardSocial ResponsibilityEnvironmental PolicyOur BusinessesEngineeringCastingsCase StudiesInvestorsAIM Rule 26 InformationShareholder InformationFinancialsCorporate GovernanceRNS AnnouncementNewsLatest newsContactContact us
Site Map
Accessibility
Privacy Notice
Home
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
Chamberlin PLC.
Chuckery Road
Walsall WS1 2DU
01922 707100
www.chamberlin.co.uk
Data Controller – Chamberlin plc.
This privacy notice sets out how Chamberlin plc. uses and protects data. Chamberlin plc. is committed to ensuring privacy is protected.
Chamberlin Plc is registered with ICO as a controller of personal information, Registration Number is Z6098534
What information do we have?
Chamberlin plc. collect and store data relating to suppliers, customers, potential customers and employees.  Data is only stored where needed and is only used to provide the legal obligations that we have with our suppliers, customers and employees.
How do we get the information and why do we have it?
Information is provided at the point that an entity becomes a supplier, customer, potential customer or employee.  Under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), the lawful basis we rely on for processing this information is:
(a)    We have a legal or contractual obligation
(b)    We have a legitimate interest
What do we do with the information we have?
We use the information provided to fulfil our obligations as a customer, supplier or employer.
How do we store your information?
Your data is securely stored until deleted.  Data is kept for a minimum period of 10 years.  We complete periodic data reviews and if data no longer required after 10 years, the data is deleted from our systems.  Your data is only shared in line with our legal obligations which might include:
Group Companies
Professional advisors (including lawyers, accountants and auditors)
Legal and Regulatory authorities
HM Revenue & Customs and other Government / State related entries
Business Sale or Transfer
Your data protection rights.
Under data protection law, you have rights including:
Your right of access – you have the right to ask us for copies of your personal information.
Your right to rectification – you have the right to ask us to complete information you think is incomplete.
Your right to erasure - You have the right to ask us to erase your personal information in certain circumstances.
Your right to restriction of processing - You have the right to ask us to restrict the processing of your information in certain circumstances.
Your right to object to processing - You have the right to object to the processing of your personal data in certain circumstances.
Your right to data portability - You have the right to ask that we transfer the information you gave us to another organisation, or to you, in certain circumstances.
Please contact our Head of Group Privacy if you wish to make a request – email carldarby@chamberlin.co.uk
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which requires your permission to be placed on your computer. The cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
No personal data is captured via the use of the cookies on our website.  A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you.  You can choose to accept or decline cookies.
How to complain.
You can complain to the ICO if you are unhappy with how we have used your data.
The ICO’s address:
Flexibility and innovative thinking develops new industrial lighting
We use cookies and track users anonymously, check this box and save to disable. We are inferring consent by continuing.
Disable non-functional cookies for this site
More Info
